[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What genus and species did the largest complete trilobite fossil ever found belong to?", "correct_answer": "Isotelus rex", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Isotelus maximus", "Isotelus brachycephalus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Snakes are very likely to attack us, regardless of whether they feel threatened or not.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the largest employer in the world.", "correct_answer": "Indian Railways", "incorrect_answers": ["Walmart", "United States Postal Service", "Microsoft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the following snakes does not belong to the Viperidae family.", "correct_answer": "Grass snake", "incorrect_answers": ["Horned adder", "Viper", "Asp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2002 movie Windtalkers, US Marines used the Navajo language as their unbreakable code.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call the base for natural logarithms ?", "correct_answer": "e", "incorrect_answers": ["i", "Pi", "3^2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Leonardo da Vinci the color green represented what?", "correct_answer": "water", "incorrect_answers": ["wealth", "wisdom", "earth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Soviet female agent falls in love with James Bond, instead of killing him, in From Russia With Love?", "correct_answer": "Tatiana Romanova", "incorrect_answers": ["Anya  Amasova", "Nadezhda Krupskaya", "Olga Milyukova"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is added to the ingredients of the Devils food cake to raise the pH level of the batter and deepen its color?", "correct_answer": "Baking soda", "incorrect_answers": ["Coffee powder", "Baking powder", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of rock is pumice?", "correct_answer": "Igneous", "incorrect_answers": ["Sedimentary", "Metamorphic", "Conglomerate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the British Overseas Territory of Bermuda, kite flying is not just a hobby, but also an important part of which holiday?", "correct_answer": "Easter", "incorrect_answers": ["Christmas", "Labour Day", "Halloween"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays the role of Rainbow Randolph in the movie Death to Smoochy?", "correct_answer": "Robin Williams", "incorrect_answers": ["Danny DeVito", "Edward Norton", "Jon Stewart"]}]